handcellphone.com 2013-06-07

# Privacy

#### Information Collection and Use

HandCellPhone.com respects the privacy of the users of this Internet site and personal electronic communication generally. HandCellPhone is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. HandCellPhone collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

#### Personal information needed for orders

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (such as name, shipping address, and e-mail address) and certain personal financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. Certain other personal information (social security number, date of birth) is required by T-Mobile for credit approval and phone activation, and is provided to that company as part of order processing.

In some instances, we may supply this personal information (social security number, date of birth) to an alternative credit provider. Aside from information as to whether a potential subscriber has been approved for credit, we do not have access to an applicant’s credit information.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We will not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘Browsing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to info@HandCellPhone.com.

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
